{
  "response_code": 0,
  "results": [
    {
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "hard",
      "category": "Entertainment: Cartoon &amp; Animations",
      "question": "Which cartoon family lives in 31 Spooner Street, Quahog, Rhode Island USA?",
      "correct_answer": "The Griffins",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "The Simpsons",
        "The Jetsons",
        "The Hills"
      ]
    },
    {
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "hard",
      "category": "Entertainment: Cartoon &amp; Animations",
      "question": "Which of these cartoon girlfriends of popular characters first appeared before their boyfriends?",
      "correct_answer": "Olive Oyl",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "Minnie Mouse",
        "Lola Bunny",
        "Daisy Duck"
      ]
    },
    {
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "hard",
      "category": "Entertainment: Cartoon &amp; Animations",
      "question": "In &quot;Gravity Falls&quot;, what does Quentin Trembley do when he is driven out from the White House?",
      "correct_answer": "Eat a salamander and jump out the window.",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "Leave in peace.",
        "Jump out the window.",
        "Release 1,000 captive salamanders into the white house."
      ]
    },
    {
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "hard",
      "category": "Entertainment: Cartoon &amp; Animations",
      "question": "Who voice acted the character Hiccup in the movie &quot;How to Train Your Dragon&quot;?",
      "correct_answer": "Jay Baruchel",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "Jack Brauchel",
        "John Powell",
        "Gerard Butler"
      ]
    },
    {
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "hard",
      "category": "Entertainment: Cartoon &amp; Animations",
      "question": "Townsend Coleman provided the voice for which turtle in the original 1987 series of &quot;Teenage Mutant Ninja Turtles&quot;?",
      "correct_answer": "Michelangelo",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "Leonardo",
        "Donatello",
        "Raphael"
      ]
    },
    {
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "hard",
      "category": "Entertainment: Cartoon &amp; Animations",
      "question": "In the web-comic Homestuck, what is the name of the game the 4 kids play?",
      "correct_answer": "Sburb",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "Homesick",
        "Husslie",
        "Hiveswap"
      ]
    },
    {
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "hard",
      "category": "Entertainment: Cartoon &amp; Animations",
      "question": "In the TV show &quot;Rick and Morty&quot;, Rick uses the catchphrase &quot;Wubba Lubba Dub Dub&quot;, which means what in Birdperson?",
      "correct_answer": "I am in great pain, please help me.",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "I pray that my life ends soon.",
        "Lets get this party started!",
        "I am suffering, please help me."
      ]
    },
    {
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "hard",
      "category": "Entertainment: Cartoon &amp; Animations",
      "question": "What was the name of Jonny&#039;s pet dog in The Adventures of Jonny Quest?",
      "correct_answer": "Bandit",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "Lucky",
        "Rocky",
        "Max"
      ]
    },
    {
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "hard",
      "category": "Entertainment: Cartoon &amp; Animations",
      "question": "What was Maggie Simpson&#039;s first canonical word, not including the Tracey Ullman shorts?",
      "correct_answer": "Daddy.",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "Sequel?",
        "Ja!",
        "Rusty!"
      ]
    },
    {
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "hard",
      "category": "Entertainment: Cartoon &amp; Animations",
      "question": "Benny, Brain, Fancy-Fancy, Spook and Choo-Choo were known associates of what Hanna Barbera cartoon character?",
      "correct_answer": "Top Cat",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "Yogi Bear",
        "Snagglepuss",
        "Scooby-Doo"
      ]
    }
  ]
}